Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Committees, 1986-2007 (Boxes 17-39)
  - Subseries B: Non-Rice, 1987-2007
    - Office of Technology Assessment Report: "Flat Panel Displays in Perspective" Oct 1995 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Office of Technology Assessment Annual Report to Congress, FY 1995. Jan 1996 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - FCCSET Report: OSTP. Federal Coordinating Council for Science, Engineering, and Technology. 1989 September 8 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology Report Drafts. 1992 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - From Red Tape to Results: Creating a Government that Works Better and Costs Less, Executive Summary. The Report of the National Performance Review. 1993 September 7 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Joint MADIC/NASA Solver Evaluation Workshop. 1993 Sept 16-17 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Letter to Josephine Abercrombie regarding President George Bush invitation to Supercomputing 1991 Conference. 1990 March 20 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Memo regarding second meeting for Advisory Panel on "Innovation and Commercialization of Emerging Technologies." 1995 April 17 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Letter from Richard Bloom, National Computer Security Center, regarding the National Information Systems Security Conference. 1998 April 1 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Letter from Rita Colwell, NSF Director, thanking Bill Joy and Ken Kennedy for PITAC leadership. 1999 September 1 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Letter from John Young, PCAST Chair, regarding annual independent assessment of the Office of Science and Technology Policy. 1999 November 4 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - General White House Materials and Letters. 1990-97 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - General E-mails regarding U.S. Government projects and White House e-mail correspondence. 1993 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Award Nomination for Sue Graham 2000 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Fellow Grade Nomination for Cheri Pancake. 2002 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Fax to Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers re: Incorrect e-mail address. 2002 December 18 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Membership 2005 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science Membership. 2005 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Association of Computing Machinery Fellow Nominations 2000 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Association of Computing Machinery Fellow Nomination for Jack Dongarra 2001 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Association of Computing Machinery Membership 2001 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Association of Computing Machinery Nomination and Recommendation (Keith Cooper) 2005 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Association of Computing Machinery Award Nomination for Marc Snir 2006 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Association of Computing Machinery Fellow Nomination for Charles Leiserson. August 2006 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - NPACI Site Visit 22-23 Oct 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - PetaFlops Systems Workshops. 22-25 April 1996 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - PetaFlops Frontier Workshop. 6 Feb 1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - PetaFlops Systems Workshops. 17-21 June 1996. (2f) (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
    - Sectioning Intro (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Sectioning Originals (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Interviews/Offers (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Vector Lecture (SIAM) (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Transparencies for Los Alamos (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Language Support for Supercomputers (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - NYU Transparencies (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - ICASE Publications, Short Course Materials 1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Papers - Best of PLDI 1979-1999 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Mapping HPF onto the Grid Paper: Kennedy and Mandal (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Yulan Zhao Revised Lazy Loop Alignment Paper 2003 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Qing Yi - LACSI Paper (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Qing Yi - Thesis Paper. "Transforming Complex Loop Nests for Locality" (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Qing Yi Paper Summer 2001 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Dominators Papers (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Elsevier Editorial System (Online System Info) (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - JPDC - EES 2004 Electronic Submission (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - JPDC - 05-201 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - JPDC-05-149 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - JPDC-05-189 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - JPDC-06-242 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - JPDC-06-236 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - JPDC 2002-0026 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - JPDC-04-87 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - JPDC Paper: MPI for Python: Performance Improvements and MPI-2 Extensions (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - In Placeness Reading (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - GNEP File (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Matlab D (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - HPF (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Reading Today (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Type Analysis/Python (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Cell Reading (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Reading (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Carol and Caitlin 4-13 June 1998 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Software prefetching (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Tallahassee materials (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Lennart Johnsson B-day Workshop at UH 2004 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - S Language Optimization meeting with Bill Szewczyk. 27 Aug 2003 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Proceedings of the Second ICSU-UNESCO International Conference (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Provost Lecture Slides. 16 Aug 1991 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Proceedings of the HTMT Project Meeting. 12-14 Jan 1998. Pasadena, CA. (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - HTMT (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - JPDC-04-10 Expanding the Reach of Grid Computing (review assignment) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - JPDC 183 Review (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - JPDC-04-34 GEL: Grid Execution Language (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - JPDC - Middleware "GrADSolve" Review Request 2003 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - JPDC 183 Review Assignments 2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - JPDC Web-Based Submission (info) 2004 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - JPDC OMR April 2003 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - JPDC Author Gateway (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - JPDC - List of SAE's June 2002 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - JPDC Minutes Ed. Board Meeting. 22 April 2003 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - JPDC Outstanding Manuscripts June 2003 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - JPDC 20 Review Assignments Sept. 2002 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - JPDC 2000-0078 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - JPDC 173 Review Assignments (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - JPDC: Improving Effective Bandwidth Through Compiler Enhancement of Global Cache Reuse by Ken Kennedy 2003 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - JPDC-05-202 (Rejected) (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - JPDC-05-133 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - JPDC-05-02 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - JPDC-05-41 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - JPDC # 0245137 Reviewer Assignment 2002 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - SP and E - Software- Practice and Experience 2001 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - JPDC 2001-0039 Review Assignments (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Schonauer, Willi. "Why I Like Vector Computers." Feb 1988 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Polychronopoulos, C. Compiler Optimizations for Enhancing Parallelism and their Impact…" Jan 1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - "Parallel Methods and Systems for Scientific/Engineering Computing" NSF Proposal 1988 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Ryder, B. and H. Pande - Interprocedural Structure of C Program (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Saltz, Joel - Principles of Runtime Support for Parallel Processors 1988 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Supercomputing 1989 Referee Evaluation Forms (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - 1989 Supercomputing Academic Papers (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - JPDC-2001-0039 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Automatic Tuning of Whole Applications Using Direct Search and Performance-based Transformation System (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - CT Watch Paper (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - The Journal of Supercomputing Correspondence 1996 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - HOPL-111 Paper (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - CCGrid 2007 Paper (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Greedy Weighted Fusion (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - HUG Special Issue "Advanced Optimization Strategies in the Rice dHPF Compiler" 2001 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Parallel Code Generation (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Fusion Paper (POPL) (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - SHPCC Tutorial (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - D Compiler Planning (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Interprocedural Analysis and Optimization (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Kernel Scheduling (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Code Generation (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Code Generation Chapter 5 Materials (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Steve Carr Talk (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - If Conversion (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Car Papers (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - HPF Chapter (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Software Prefetching (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Linear Diophantine Equations (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Steve Carr (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Parallel Code Gen Example (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Teraflop Computing: Fact and/or Fantasy (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Interprocedural Algorithms (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - "Application Development Support Based on High Performance Software Integration." 12 April 2000 (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - CT Watch Quarterly Nov 2005 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - "Triangular Decomposition Methods for Solving Reducible Nonlinear Systems of Equations." May 1994 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Chapter 4 Materials - Scalar Analysis (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Various Academic Papers 1978-1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - "The Euro, the Year 2000, and the Software Personnel Shortage" by Capers Jones. 2 March 1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - "Federated Search of Scientific Literature: A Retrospective on the Illinois Digital Library Project" and 2 other articles on Supercomputers. 1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - CRPC Automatic and Interactive Parallelization by Kathryn S. McKinley April 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Series III: Rice Computational Science Department, 1981-2007 (Boxes 39-41)
  - "Exploring Gender Differences in Reactions to Engineering Pedagogy" by Amy Ballew (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Rice University Documents/Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - 1994 Post-Graduate Study - Career Services Center (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Rice Curriculum (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Comp 515 Spring 1996 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - CSD (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - CS Graduate Applicants 1993 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Black Friday (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - PhD Program Requirements - 1993 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Revision (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Teaching (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Equipment Orders (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Rice University Media Resource Guide (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Fellows Report (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Fellows Subcommittee 1999 (2f) (Box 39, Folder 20-21)
  - SPA Memos to Executive Committee April 1991 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Programs for Women (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Rice Department of Computer Science Brochure (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - CS Curriculum Revision (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Minority Institutions (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Research Funding (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - The Rice School Shared Decision Making Team (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - K-8 Meeting. 3 Sept 1996 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Student Support Plan 1990 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - CS Dept Temporary Space Use 1990 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Rice CS History Project-Melissa Kean (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Oral History Project (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - "Dependence-based Code Generation for a CELL Processor" by Yuan Zhao and Ken Kennedy (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Jones School Plan (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Rice University and the Texas Medical Center (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Parallel Processing Qual (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Keith's ARPA WP (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report due 3 Dec 2001 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report to Chair 2002 (Box 39, Folder 40-41)
  - Ken Kennedy Annual Report to Chair Dec 2002 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report to Chair 2002 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Annual Report to Chair 2004 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Annual Report to Chair 2006 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Kennedy Journal Articles and Conference Papers with graduate students 2005 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Comp Eng Brochure (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Sorensen Comp. Sci and Eng. Article (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Computational Science Degree Program (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Mathematics Program Proposal (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Minorities' Programs (Richard) (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Thresher Salary Survey (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - K-8 Rice Plan (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - "The Coming Generation of Massively Parallel Supercomputers" Presentation slides by Ken Kennedy (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - CRPC - Making Parallel Computing Truly Usable (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Radha's Visit (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - ST-HEC Annual Report 2006 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Rice University Computer Science Technical Reports 1991 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - BNR - Agreement (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - The Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Advanced Facility for CS (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Myers Visit (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Accreditation (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - CITI History (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Former Students (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - PhD Admissions - CS Department 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - India Meeting (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ken's Telescoping Lang. follow-up presentation 2004 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Rice University Computer Science Space Needs and Allocations 1983-1990 (2f) (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
  - Computation - IBM Facility Eng Proposal (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - CS Committee 1981 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Salaries 1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Budget Materials (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Fund II Accounts (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Teaching (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - C Exam - Optimization Spring 1988 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - 1987-88 Qualifying Exam Syllabus (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Exams (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Department Publicity (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - General Research Procedures (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Chairman's Duties (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Attendee Lists (Snowbird) (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Conway Survey of CS Programs (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - 1987 Citation Survey (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Surveys (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Taulbee Survey 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Research Funding (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Enhancement Program (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Department Report (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Engineering School Grants (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Chairpersons Meetings (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence October 1988 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Business Manager Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Minutes (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Policy on Appointments, Promotions, and Retention (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Summary of Grants and Contracts in Engineering 1988 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - "Multi-Processor Cluster Computing" NSF Proposal. 19 Oct 1993 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Addendum to RI Proposal. 25 April 1995 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Teaching Load in Computer Science (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Graduate Student Reform: A Compromise Proposal to the Computer Science Faculty (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Student Meetings 1993 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Student Progress Reports March 1994 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Topics (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Proposed Changes to Graduate Program Requirements 1993 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Student Statistics (Rice, PhD) (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Matlab Biweekly Teleconferences 2005 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Computational Science Degree Program (Ellen) (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Student Profiles for Recruitment Publications (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - HPF HOPL Paper Teleconference. 13 July 2006 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - CS Affiliates Day (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - General files (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Keith and Joe Warren Promotions (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - CSD Annual Report 1996- CRPC Info (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - CSD Annual Report 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - CSD Annual Report 1997 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - President's Report 1998 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - CSD/President's Report 1999 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Positions (Advertised) (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - General Employment (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Assistant Professor Examples (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Elana Granston - tenure-track/research faculty candidate 1991 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - "Multi Processor Cluster Computing" proposal to NSF (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Blue Chip Applicant Recruitment (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Job Permission (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - 1990 Commencement (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - 1993 Commencement (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - 1995 Commencement (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - CS Faculty Recruiting (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Rice Presidential Search (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Comp 505 Spring '03 Evaluations (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - 2004 Grad Admissions - Kennedy (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - CS Grad Recruiting (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - S and E IT Meeting (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - N.I. In-Place Study (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - CITI Interview (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - HPC Faculty Search (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - CS affiliates contact information (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Penny Anderson Resignation (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - "Promoting National Minority Leadership in Science and Engineering" (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - ITAC Article March 2005 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Richard Tapia - Hispanic Engineer National Achievement Award for Education File 1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - The Technology Opportunity Institute Board Meeting. 2006 February 15 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Meeting with Stan Ahalt (OSC) 17 Sept 2004 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Leadership, correspondence, adminstration 2006 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Thinking Machines Visit. 23 May 1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Items for Ken to Review (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Pre-NPEBC Planning Program Grant (P20) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Breakfast with Dr. Arden Bement. 11 Sept 2006 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - India Visit Info (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy Biographies - 2008 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Intel: Restricted (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - OT Assessment Advisory Panel (US Congress) (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Ken's Book (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Book Corrections (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Books Comments from Comp 515 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Class 515 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Ch 4 - Preliminary Transformations (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - U.S. House of Representatives Ken Kennedy Testimony (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Computer Science 515 Syllabus and Chapter Photocopies (2f) (Box 41, Folder 19-20)
  - Proposal for BS degree in Computer Science (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Getting Acquainted Weekend March 2004 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - People/Companies - correspondence, memos (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Committees (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Users Committee Meeting. 19 Jan 1994 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Recruiting - Kath Knobe, CRL. 14 Dec 2000 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Paracel Visit April 2004 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Dean of Engineering Faculty Meeting 2005 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Meeting - new IT manager 2005 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - High Technology Education Coalition (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Talks (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Facilities proposal 1992 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - C.E. Building meeting - Kennedy slides. 3 Feb 1994 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Ken - Smalley Building (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Joint Fundraising (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Facilities Proposal (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Rice University Campaign for Computational Engineering (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Thank You - Ken to Zumwalts (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Dedication Day - Computational Engineering Building 1 Nov 1986 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Groundbreaking - Computational Engineering Building (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Computational Engineering Building - General (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Series IV: Teaching Career, 1973-2006 (Boxes 42-44)
  - Optimization; Advanced Optimization Course. Fall, Spring 1973. (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Optimization; Advanced Optimization Course. Fall, Spring 1973. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Optimization 111. 1973. (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Optimization 111. 1973. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - MASC 381 Probability. Spring 1973. (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - MASC 381 Probability. Spring 1973. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - MASC/ELEC 521. 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - MASC/ELEC 421 Compilers. Spring 1976. (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - MASC/ELEC 421 Compilers. Spring 1976. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - MASC/ELEC 421 Compilers. Spring 1976. (Folder 3) (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - MASC/COMP 421 Systems Programming. Fall 1977-Fall 1980 (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - MASC/COMP 421 Systems Programming. Fall 1977-Fall 1980. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - MASC 451. Fall 1979 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - COMP 518. Fall 1979-Fall 1984 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - MASC 460. Fall 1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - MASC/COMP 321 Advanced Programming. Spring 1980. (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - MASC/COMP 321 Advanced Programming. Spring 1980. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - COMP 621. Spring 1981 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - MASC/COMP 523. Fall 1982. (Folder 1) (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - MASC/COMP 523. Fall 1982. (Folder 2) (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - MASC/COMP 523. Fall 1982. (Folder 3) (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - COMP 321. Fall 1983, Fall 1984. (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - COMP 321. Fall 1983, Fall 1984. (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - COMP 420. Spring 1984. (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - COMP 420. Spring 1984. (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Advanced Topics in Compiler Construction. 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - CS 155/CS 260. Fall 1984, Fall 1985. (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - CS 155/CS 260. Fall 1984, Fall 1985. (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - CS 155/CS 260. Fall 1984, Fall 1985. (Folder 3) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - COMP 522 Database Project. Spring 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - COMP 380/480. Spring 1988. (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - COMP 380/480. Spring 1988. (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - COMP 380/480. Spring 1988. (Folder 3) (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - COMP 380 Concrete Mathematics. 1988 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - COMP 480 Concrete Mathematics. 1988 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Keith Cooper's Class (9/16/92) (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - COMP 314 Applied Algorithms and Data Structures. 1996 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - COMP 615 Parallel Programming Systems. 1998 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - COMP 314. Fall 1998 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - COMP 515 Advanced Compilation for Vector Parallel Processors. Spring 1999 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - COMP 310. Fall 1995 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - COMP 412 Textbook. Fall 2000. (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - COMP 412 Textbook. Fall 2000. (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - COMP 412 Compiler Construction. Fall 2003 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - COMP 412 Textbook. Fall 2003 (Folder 1) (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - COMP 412 Textbook. Fall 2003 (Folder 2) (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Course Evaluations Fall 1979 to Spring 1990 (Folder 1) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Course Evaluations Fall 1979 to Spring 1990 (Folder 2) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Course Evaluations Fall 1979 to Spring 1990 (Folder 3) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Class Handouts. 1990 April 10 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Class Handouts. 1990 January 25 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Class Handouts. 1990 January 18 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - COMP 515 - Advanced Compilation for Vector and Parallel Processors Syllabus. Spring 1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - COMP 212 Program 2 and 3 Handouts. Fall 1992 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Keith Cooper's Class Notes. 1992 September 14 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - COMP 515 - Chapter 2: Dependence, Parallelization and Vectorization. Fall 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - COMP 515 - Chapter 4: Scalar Symbolic Analysis. Fall 1992 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - COMP 310 Laboratory 2. Fall 1993 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - COMP 515 Class Notes. Fall 1993. (2f) (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
  - COMP 515 - Advanced Compilation for Vector and Parallel Processors Syllabus, Class Textbook and Notes. Fall 1993 (2f) (Box 44, Folder 15-16)
  - COMP 310 - Programming Studio Syllabus. Fall 1994 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - COMP 310: Guidelines for C++ Program Style. Fall 1994 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - COMP 310: Grading for Comp 310 Labs. Fall 1994 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - COMP 310: Guidelines for Specifications. Fall 1994 (Box 44, Folder 20)